<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tool-bundle create-date="2020-04-16">
  <procedures>
    <procedure-definition id="FSS-TS-PF-GEN" name="* Pass &amp; Fail Special Codes Generator" category="Gradebook" javasource-file="PassFailSpecialCodes.java" input-file="*Pass&amp;FailSpecialCodesGeneratorInput.xml" weight="1" description="&lt;h2&gt;This tool allows districts to generate special codes for teachers. An explanation of the tool's behavior and input options is below:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10px&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Customization of this tool is not supported at this time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Behavior&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tool looks for active staff by both statuses on staff and user account records. If the staff is marked as active by the district preference, and enabled for the user's login record, they will be collected for application. Note that additional criteria can be applied to limit which staff this tool affects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the staff are collected, the tool will begin to generate 2 special codes for staff: A 'pass' and 'fail' code. These are generated at &lt;em&gt;Staff View &gt; Tools &gt; Special Codes&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool is hard programmed to set these codes to be exempt from caluclations, not counted as missing, and color coded dark blue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool allows for only a single code to be entered, however if both are missing, a unique exception error is provided to prevent the tool from being run. The exception you will see will begin with the following: &quot;This tool is intended to generate at least one code. Please supply a code when running this tool.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Included is a safety to identify a matching code (if previously run), or a similar code and prevents adding your new code to the staff. A message is provided to identify which staff have this match for you to review.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool can be interrupted, and will attempt to roll back any codes already added. Please be careful to not rely on this function, and carefully review your inputs before running.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inputs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;School &lt;/strong&gt;- If blank, it will run for the entire district. If schools are provided, only staff at those schools will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: pick lists allow for multiple selections.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to limit staff by type?&lt;/strong&gt; - Selecting this checkbox enables a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;multiple &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;selection picklist for limiting which staff to include based on the district's type codes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to limit staff by department code?&lt;/strong&gt; - Selecting this checkbox enables a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;multiple &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;selection picklist for limiting which staff to include based on the district's department codes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to limit staff by bargaining unit?&lt;/strong&gt; - Selecting this checkbox enables a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;multiple &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;selection picklist for limiting which staff to include based on the district's bargaining unit codes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter the code to generate for a PASSING/FAILING grade&lt;/strong&gt; - This is a text box that allows any entry. It is best to keep these codes to 4 or less characters. Again, &lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;one of these fields can be left blank&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preview Mode&lt;/strong&gt; - On by default, this selection prevents the tool from saving any data to the database, and thus committing your district to the entered codes. Please note that this tool is not capable of undoing code generation. Manual deletion or a data restore are the only way to revert incorrect code entries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provide verbose logging when run?&lt;/strong&gt; - This selection provides a very detailed breakdown of this tool's functioning. It is primarily meant for troubleshooting purposes.&lt;/p&gt;" schedulable="false" disable-autokill="false" />
  </procedures>
</tool-bundle>

